Megan Pardy Gokcu

17 Chesley Avenue · Somersworth, NH 03878 · 603-923-0446 · meg.pardy@gmail.com

An energetic professional with a commitment to driving growth and success by drawing on 9+ years of experience working for non-profit and for-profit institutions. Superior ability to learn and adapt to new software systems and technologies within a short timeframe. Can easily integrate into new and unique environments and procedures. Excellent background leading, supporting, and building strong, dedicated teams that work together to overcome obstacles and achieve ambitious goals.

Core competencies include:

- Marketing & Branding
- Graphic Design
- Website Design & Development
- Media & Public Relations
- Database Building & Administration
- Copy Editing
- Social Media

Technological competencies include:

- HTML5&CSS
- Adobe (InDesign, Premiere, Photoshop, Illustrator, Acrobat)
- Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access)
- Final Cut Pro
- Drupal
- Salesforce

- Analytics
- Project Management
- Workflow Improvement
- Event Planning & Coordination
- Orientation & On-boarding
- Revenue Optimization
- Proactive Issue Resolution
- Predictive Response
- Outlook
- Ellucian Degree Works
- Banner Student & Finance
- Xtender
- Handshake

-PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE -

UNIVERSITY OF NEW HAMPSHIRE, Durham, NH

Marketing Manager (7/2019 to Present)

Supports the strategic and operational objectives of Career and Professional Success by providing professional specialized creative communication services that include all of the following: digital, social media and print publications. Ensures that the virtual and written presence has key themes and messages that match the mission, marketing strategies and communication goals. Designs, manages, and maintains the Career and Professional Success website. Serve as the main point of contact and relationship manager for UNH Web and Mobile Development office. Execute all visual design stages from concept to final approval. Maintains and analyzes Google Analytics statistics for the website, providing reports monthly for leadership. Manages Career and Professional Success presence within the UNH-wide publishing platform, UNH Today. Maintains Career and Professional Success events within UNHwide master calendar, Wildcat Link, and other digital calendars. Designs and creates a wide variety of effective print marketing materials that reflect the brand of Career and Professional Success. Provides print collateral support for college-specific and university-wide event marketing, from posters, flyers, and campus signage. Collaborates extensively with other communication professionals across the university to promote career services messaging within additional university publications. Coordinates relationships with various promotional vendors, including UNH Print Services, Creates content for Career and Professional Success social media accounts. Shoots and edits photo and video content to engage all target audiences via social channels. Maintains social media monthly analytics reports to provide to Director of Marketing. Assist with hiring, directing and evaluating student workers and/or other staff, including interviewing, training, advising on new procedures, coordinating information, and shifting work to accommodate workload needs.

Marketing, Events, and Communication Specialist (4/2017 to 7/2019)

Develops and implements a Career and Professional Success marketing plan to substantially impact student engagement and provide consistent messaging university-wide. Introduces new and exciting promotional ideas to help further establish the Career and Professional Success brand, both internally and externally. Conceptualizes engaging content for all target audiences across the various social media accounts and facilitate content development through graphic design and media production. Web developer for the Career and Professional Success website, and serves as point of contact with UNH Web Services office. Oversees the planning and logistics of all university-wide recruiting events, including the bi-annual Career & Internship Fair, including coordinating the relationships with various vendors, including print, parking, catering, venue, and security. Provides branding oversight on all projects. Manages designated projects and improves project outcomes by establishing standards – delivery, quality, issue resolution, etc. Maintains program plans and streamlines processes and assists with process improvements. Analyzes data and develops regular reporting. Coordinates shared messaging and makes sure that all communication is consistent across team.

Selected accomplishments:

- · Successfully rebranded the department to fall within University of New Hampshire standards and create a more appealing aesthetic.
- \cdot Researched and found highly competitive vendors for supplies and services, saving the department budget without sacrificing quality.
- · Digitized multiple print collateral pieces to circulate through social media and on website.
- · Established as primary contact and manager for all website questions and updates.

Professional Experience Continued

Business Service Assistant (7/2015 to 4/2017)

Maintained a positive culture within the clinical and administrative areas of the business, responsible for ensuring that faculty and students have a positive experience. Oversaw the University Credit Card program for the College of Life Sciences and Agriculture, provided orientations to new credit card users, document compilation and archiving, auditing, coding, and data entry. Performed responsibilities in a fast paced environment while also acting as receptionist, administrator, and staff liaison. Met the needs of the college throughout a variety of complex weekly, monthly, annual deadlines.

Selected accomplishments:

- · Integrated into business finance within a relatively short time frame. Established positive relationships with purchase card users by providing on-boarding, frequent coaching, and accessible assistance throughout day to day operations.
- · Problem solved how to improve the financial accuracy and integrity by meticulously reviewing processes to pinpoint and immediately resolve discrepancies.
- · Updated antiquated processes to streamline procedures and developed electronic workflow to expedite auditing, coding, and archiving. Proactively in process of developing a paperless system for roll out.
- ·Cultivated and maintained relationships with product and service vendors to expedite document collection as a way to support the faculty and researchers at the college.

GRANITE STATE COLLEGE, Rochester, NH

Administrative Assistant/Grant Administrator/Admissions/Program Advisor (7/2012 to 7/2015)

Expertly balanced a wide range of responsibilities including organizing special events, processing and evaluating new student and grant applications, daily registration, student advising, transcript evaluation, over the phone orientations, student outreach and recruitment, database management, and data archiving. Developed promotional and marketing materials through graphic design, organized campaigns, reorganized website navigation and web page design, worked in tandem with the Dean to achieve program and grant approval, created and maintained tracking sheets to accurately monitor student progression and completion throughout program. Evaluated registration, turnover, and application data to make projections, and locate areas of improvement. Set up and maintained relationships with childcare facilities throughout the state to support grant applicants.

Selected accomplishments:

- · Hand-selected to assist with on-boarding of new technologies throughout tenure. Representative for the School of Education at institution wide orientations and liaison between organizing members and the department. Provided training of new software and policies to the School of Education Staff after orientations were complete. Trained to act as a backend administrator for Salesforce and Ellucian DegreeWorks
- · Introduced new office policies and procedures to increase efficiency in the development of the office. Developed office playbook and reference manual.

LONG ISLAND UNIVERSITY, Brooklyn, NY

Program Support (9/2010 to 5/2012)

Supported the Administrative Assistant of the Media Arts Department by taking over such responsibilities as reception, copying, filing, document archival, interoffice mail pick up and delivery, scheduling, meeting arrangements, and special projects and events.

Selected accomplishments:

· Successfully redesigned the Graduate Requirement Forms to reflect the current curriculum and update the language with more user-friendly syntax.

-EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND-

Project ManagementGRANITE STATE COLLEGE, Concord, NH

Master of Science (Anticipated Summer of 2020)

Media Arts LONG ISLAND UNIVERSITY, Brooklyn, NY Bachelor of Arts Degree (2012) Summa Cum Laude